linksgolf-ireland.com 2011-03-20

# Privacy Policy | Links Golf Ireland | A member of the Emerald Elite Limited Group

## Collection and use of personal information by Emerald Elite Ltd

Emerald Elite Ltd does not collect any personal data about you on this website, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us or by using our online comment/feedback forms).

Any personal information which you provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, except if required by law, and is used by the Emerald Elite Ltd only for the purpose for which you provided it.

## Access to Personal Information

Information that you supply online by email or electronic form may be retained within the case records of Emerald Elite Ltd in connection with the statutory activities of the company.

These case records are confidential to the company and are not released to third parties. On application under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 you may request to be provided with a copy of the data concerning you that is retained by the company.

You also have the right to request that any data concerning you, which is incorrectly retained, is promptly corrected in our records.

## Collection and use of technical information

This website does not use cookies, apart from temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor's web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited.

Technical details in connection with visits to this website are logged by our internet service provider for our statistical purposes. No information is collected that could be used by us to identify website visitors. The technical details logged are confined to the following items:

  * The IP address of the visitor's web server
  * The top-level domain name used (for example .ie, .com)
  * Clickstream data which shows the traffic of visitors around this web site (for example pages accessed and documents downloaded)
  * The type of web browser used by the website visitor
  * The version of the operating system used by the visitor

Emerald Elite Ltd makes no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details listed above with any individual.

It is the policy of the organisation never to disclose such technical information in respect of individual website visitors to any third party (apart from our internet service provider, which records such data on our behalf and which is bound by confidentiality provisions in this regard), unless obliged to disclose such information by a rule of law.

The technical information will be used only by this organization, and only for statistical and other administrative purposes. You should note that technical details, which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual, do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection Acts, 1988 & 2003.

## Glossary of Technical Terms

### Web browser

The piece of software you use to read web pages. Examples are Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox, Netscape Navigator and Opera.

### IP address

The identifying details for your computer (or your internet company's computer), expressed in "internet protocol" code (for example 192.168.72.34). Every computer connected to the web has a unique IP address, although the address may not be the same every time a connection is made.

### Cookies

Small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a web site. Cookies can be read by the web site on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that the web site can "remember" you on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the web site.
